<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><plugin-repository><ff>"Graphics"</ff><category name="Graphics"><idea-plugin downloads='9865' size='68848' date='1372078495000' url=''><name>SvgViewer 2</name><id>SvgViewer 2</id><description><![CDATA[An updated version of the SVG Viewer plugin originally released by Andrew Armstrong back in 2004 (I attempted to contact him but his listed email address is no longer valid) This release works with the current versions of the Intellij platform and runs in Intellij and WebStorm. It seems to have trouble in AppCode due to a missing Batik dependency. However I was unable to find a 'depends' node in the plugin.xml file that indicated it works with all Intellij platforms except AppCode so I simply left it out, indicating it works for Intellij only. UPDATE: I've added some dependencies so that this can be used with WebStorm and PhpStorm. It will not work on AppCode, even if it shows up as being available in the browser repository for that product.]]></description><version>2.0.3</version><vendor email='billdwhite@gmail.com' url=''>Bill White</vendor><idea-version min="n/a" max="n/a" since-build='111.1' /><change-notes><![CDATA[<ul> 
 <li>2.0.3 - fixes contributed by Vlad Rassokhin; added missing about html page</li> 
 <li>2.0.2 - added button to toggle background to allow better visibility of svgs with light colors; adding other web platforms</li> 
 <li>2.0.1 - adjusted image size to suppress log warnings</li> 
 <li>2.0 - first release</li> 
</ul>]]></change-notes><depends>com.intellij.modules.lang</depends><depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends><depends>com.intellij.modules.ultimate</depends><rating>00</rating></idea-plugin></category><ff>"Misc"</ff><category name="Misc"><idea-plugin downloads='35527' size='148963' date='1392794396000' url='https://github.com/syllant/idea-plugin-remotesynchronizer'><name>RemoteSynchronizer</name><id>RemoteSynchronizer</id><description><![CDATA[RemoteSynchronizer plugin allows you to synchronize files with remote locations. Instead of manually copying files from your proje